Hello everyone! This is Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love.
Yes! So today, I'm here for the Odaiba adventure in 2024.
Well, here it is! This way! We are here at the Surprise Grand Prix Museum 2024!
Yay! I wanted to come, so I asked the staff to let me.
Then, they said it was okay,
I would like to thank everyone involved in the Dokyu Grand Prix.
Thank you very much.
Yes, let me tell you why I came,
I came here because of my appearance at the DQ Grand Prix,
I was surprised to see my face on display when I appeared at the DQ Grand Prix,
I also heard that it is now available as a free book,
I would like to introduce this to you all.
I would like to introduce it to all of you and hope that you will come and visit,
Today, I would like to report on it.
By the way, how did you feel when you heard that the face was going to be exhibited?
Well, um, the manager sent me those candidate faces,
There were a few that were really bad.
That was the only one that didn't make it,
But, you know, the faces I carefully selected are supposed to be on display.
Here are the photos of the ones that just barely made it into the office.
I'm off.
Here we go.
This is the entrance. Let's go in.
I'm going to go in. I'm going to go in.
Rattle, rattle, rattle.
It's cool, it's cool, it's cool, it's so cool in here.
Age limit is 3 and up. Wait and see, this attraction is really gonna surprise you.
Wait, look, this attraction is really gonna freak you out.
What do you mean?
Well, we're going to go ahead and do it.
There's Mr. Hasegawa.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I take a picture?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm so happy.
Speaking of the Surprise Grand Prix...
I'm here with Mr. Hasegawa, who's been very kind to me.
Heart.
What's this?
This way.
I'm going to try this.
GO!
Oh, wow!
Aaaaah!
Wait a minute.
Surprise!
You mean this is real, right?
I hope you all get to experience it.
I'd like you all to get down on that stoop and experience it like I did.
Get punched in the face... just like I did.
What's this?
They say it's aimed right at your face.
They say the air is dizzying.
I'd like to experience this.
I'm still scared.
Around here?
I'm going. Thank you very much.
I'm scared.
Oh, my God!
Scary.
Crazy.
ahaha
Strong.
Strong
I think it's too strong
State of development
This is fun!
Nice booth.
My hair was a mess.
Okay, let's move on.
Oh, there it is.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
There it is!
Oh, my gosh! Wait!
Oh, wait, that's great!
Look at this!
Wait, you can hear me.
Wait.
BGM.
Hey, shut up!
BGM
Equal Love Takamatsu City
Artistic Screaming Gallery!
I'm so happy!
It's a little bit like a hallway.
It's like a world, and it's my gallery.
And my screams are in there too...
Okay, let's start from here.
This way.
Shut up!
Me, me, me.
Can you hear me? Is this bad for everyone?
Oh, it's me.
November 11th, 2023.
That's when Perrotaro was on the air, right?
Hey.
10, 2022.
The one at the car.
Wait.
The meter's popping out, too.
The meter's popping out in 3D, too.
Hey.
This is really a face with arms.
It's obvious.
Did you do it?
You're not doing it.
But I'm doing it.
And if I did, I'd be a genius, wouldn't I? On the contrary.
It's very well done.
What's your favorite face, Hitori?
My personal favorite is this gallery.
In the ice cream hallway.
I think this one.
I think this is the one with the eyeballs popping out in 3D.
His eyeballs are popping out.
This one, his eyeballs are physically popping out.
This is my favorite.
Shut up! I'm not giving it to you! Shut up!
But I was really surprised at that point.
I didn't know how much to add or subtract, I just did it.
I guess screaming calms me down a little.
This is how my gallery hallway looked like
with screaming music playing behind me the whole time.
Isn't it amazing?
Look, it's my zone.
These are the speakers.
It's so loud.
I'd like you to come through here.
I'm so happy for you.
That's great.
So I'm out.
I'm so tired.
I've only been here about 10 minutes.
I wasn't there that long.
I was so satisfied, so satisfied, so satisfied.
It was like a lie.
I was so happy.
I don't know if I'd like him if he stayed with us any longer.
I might even get sick of him.
Surprise Grand Prix Museum 2024
There's more goodies to come after this.
Thank you for watching.
Let's go to the merchandise booth.
We're here at the merchandise booth.
Wait, I've never seen this before.
It's a free book!
I'll touch it.
Here's my CAR free-form book.
It's really a free book!
It really is a free book.
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey, shut up.
I'm glad there's so many of them.
I told my parents
I told them I'd be there.
My mom got two books.
Your dad bought 10.
What are you gonna do with all that?
I don't know.
After seeing this museum.
After seeing the museum, you can take one of these books home as a souvenir.
A copy for each family.
Yes, please.
That's right.
Anna has a notebook called "Equal Love Notebook.
This time...
She wants to use it as an Equal Love Notebook.
I'd like to buy one for Anna as a souvenir.
I'd like to buy one for her.
I'd like to buy one as a souvenir for Anne.
I always have this with me when I'm at an important engine show, like an Ikoram concert.
Thirteen points.
Hey, shut up.
Stand over here, please.
I could hear you the whole time I was in the gift store.
I'm so sorry.
I'm getting a headache.
Thank you very much.
I bought it!
fluent
Thirteen books.
It's good?
I'm making the most of it.
It's done.
It's nice, there's a place to write your name here.
Just in time.
All Abu Hitomi Takamatsu.
Ta-da! I'll put this on the wall.
Thank you very much.
I got it!
Wait a minute.
I've never seen this before.
I know this one!
Mitarashi, too big cushion.
If you're ready to buy one, please contact our staff.
Please ask a member of our staff if you are ready to purchase.
It's the first time I've seen something like this written on it.
We all know how much it costs.
77,000 yen.
That's a lot!
You want to buy it? Expenses?
It's cute, but...
What do you think? I'm sure you'd like to sell it, wouldn't you, Surprise Grand Prix?
Yes, please.
Please, please, please.
The fans of Equal Love will buy it.
So come on in and get ready to buy!
It's a little too big. I have 163, but that's all I have.
Well, I'm not sure I'm ready for this.
Well, I had a great time at the Surprise Grand Prix Museum 2024!
It all happened so fast, but it was so satisfying.
It's already ranked as the number one summer memory of 2024!
It was so much fun!
I was so happy to get to the merchandise booth!
I don't want to hear your voice anymore, but I...
I want you to come, for sure!
I'm sure you'll see a lot of my gallery and
and get a free book too!
Thank you so much, Mr. Surprise Grand Prix!
I don't know if there will be another one.
I'll save my voice.
Odaiba Adventure 2024
Dokkiri Grand Prix Museum 2024
Thank you very much for coming.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.